the trek to the Shadow Gate is a three day affair
I fear that Slimelord may be well ahead of us by then
I'll not rely on my boots for this journey
the Eye of Zaranthril
Brother Braythwaite
perhaps it would be unwise to bring a third Nether-Gem right to the Slimelord
we've no choice dear brother
time is ticking as The Slime™️ is thickening
once you cross into the realm of shadows
you'll have no backing
not from the Council of the Shard
not from the Porkwatch
if you've not returned in an hour's time
dear Braythwaite
we will light the fires of Porkfort and send all its footmen to Shadow's Gate
it must be so
it is what the Shard demands
then by the power of the Shard
you shall prevail
go with the Shard on your side
by the power of Zaranthril
take me now to the realm of shadows
I fear that death awaits him
it must be so brother to him
or The Slime™️ awaits us all
hello Gorlock
do you know me
you go by many names
"Light-Bringer"
"the Scythe of Tharnak
Braythwaite
I can smell the Shard on your robes
we've no time for pleasantries
I've come for Slimelord
don't ever mention that name again