it's no use Thurandrar
I have the Robanduthrix Crystal
without it you can't draw your power from the Shadow Realm
except I have the Jewel of Grendulem
which allows me to travel between realms
including the Shadow Realm
but that's useless
unless you have
the Bibbulin Crystal
which allows me to access the power of any adjacent realm remotely
but you're forgetting one thing Thurandrar
it's impossible to wield two power crystals
unless you have
The eye of Krizzenthus
which allows me to wield multiple power crystals at the same time
impossible
that crystal was forged in the Shadow Realm
the only way you'd have access to it is if you had
the Robanduthrix Crystal
this entire time
but that's impossible
I have the Robanduthrix Crystal
the only way you can deceive me into thinking I didn't
is if you had
the Jewel of Snabe
which allows me to cast a projection of any power crystal
no
noooo
do not fret my child
you shall forget this entire interaction once I call on the power
of Rendubreeb's Ruby