where is the Slime Lord
how foolish that you think me an ally
I don't seek your allegiance
I seek the Lord of the Slime
you mock me Light-bringer
you come to my prison and ask for a favor
you chose this cell the day
you turn to the Jeremys against the king
the Shard affords you much knowledge
yet you know so little
I'm not here to adjudicate the past
I'm here because at present the Slime Lord threatens all I hold dear
and you seek my sympathy
all I hold dear exists beyond the veil that I cannot penetrate
even the shadows no longer answer to me
you gave him the Shadow Stone
he is a demon
Gorlock
you must tell me where he is
the Slime Lord threatens all within the realm of light
including that which you hold dear
the shadows may bind you now Golock
but there is still fire within you
I know it
it burns for Maywynn
wherever she dwells
you took her from me when you locked me in this dungeon
the Slime™️ consumes all Gorlock
it is indiscriminate
it swallows up all within its path
and then it devours the light
you're using her to trick me
just like he did
Slimelord promised you Maywynn
he said if I gave him the stone
he would open a door between the realms of light and shadow
that I may feel her warmth again
but it was a lie
I am fighting for the same realm your heart longs for
please help me
he already has the heart of Asloendrath
and now he has the Shadow Stone
and he's 3 days ahead of us
three days
he took the stone from me
seven years ago
that's impossible
he is a demon