thank you for agreeing to meet me here
High Councilman
The Council of the Shard relies on the Porkwatch
the Watch should be able to rely on the Council
that we can, Ormid
at least in my experience
last I checked, the Darkwoods did not fall under the Porkwatch's jurisdiction
why are we here
that it doesn't, Ormid
but some conversations that require discretion
and there's no place quite as discreet as these Dark Woods
all right Thorranbarth
you've got my attention
as you are well aware
three nights ago
gentlemen identified as members of the Slimeguard
attempted to steal the Crown of Elgnar
my understanding is they've been thrown into the Porkhold
pending a further investigation by the Porkwatch
aye
but this morning we found the cells empty
they've escaped
I'm not so sure it was an escape, councilman
the locks have not been tampered with and the hinges are intact
are you suggesting the Porkwatch has been compromised
I'm not suggesting anything
high Councilman
I only relay what my eyes have seen
is there a Man of the Pork that you've deemed untrustworthy
not until this morning when I saw those bare cells
who's your suspect, Thorranbarth
we've got new blood on the Watch
a young lad who joined after the harvest
when his father sold off his snail farm
and you think him untrustworthy
no one's laid eyes on him for two nights
I just checked his father's house
up the ridge
and he's not seen him since last night when he left in a hurry
does he have any known affiliates
someone he might be working with
or for
I've not seen him in the company of questionable characters myself
Ormid
but there's a feeling I can't quite shake
I mentioned his father sold off his snail farm
that was some time ago
but last time I saw the lad
there was a residue on his robes
far to be it for me to point fingers
especially at members of the High Council of the Shard
but tell me this, brother Ormid
when's the last time you saw
Slimelord