Slime Lord has been in possession of the Shadow Stone
for seven years
before I gave him the stone
the shadows spoke to me
what did they say
they told me only of things within the gloom and the murk
liars and cheats
thieves and scoundrels
death and decay
then the Lord of the Slime™ offered you
her
Maywynn
he said I would feel her embrace again
but he never returned
seven years I've sat here
rotting in the shadows
awaiting her glow
I see now the tapestry unfurling before me
it was Slime Lord who refused to sign the Accords
Accords that would have sealed the Shadow Gate forever
but he wanted to get to you
he is a viper
he speaks with a tongue of fire
free me from this prison
and I'll destroy him myself
you know I cannot
grateful as I am for your knowledge
it will not save you
then promise me
you will save Maywynn
when the Slime War is over
all will be saved
very well
just tell me how
how the man whose heart beats for Maywynn
could raise the army of a thousand Jeremys
I did it for her
men from your realm came in the night
they took everything
you'd have done the same
who were these men