the slime gate must be closed
I believe it is in the interest of the High Council
of the Order of the Shard that it be sealed immediately
all in favor say aye
aye
nay
what brings you here Slime Lord
last I checked I am a member of this council
you forfeited your seat the moment you refused to sign the accords
I'll sign the accords once I've set my peace
he is a traitor
he has no place on this council
the Shard demands of us understanding
allow the man to speak
speak now Slime Lord
then be gone from this place
the Slime Gate cannot be closed without the talisman
and last I checked it resides within the Shadow Realm
with the full resources of the Pork Watch on our side
we shall acquire the Shadow Stone
there may be no trust between us
but surely
this council is not so foolish as to tarry with the Shadow Lord himself
we can handle Gorlock
allow me to speak to Gorlock
we have a storied history
and perhaps I can restore some of the good will between us
surely you cannot be considering this arrangement
he is the Slime Lord
he seeks to keep the slime gate open
merely because he draws his power from the slime
what will it be High Councilman
will you start a war with Gorlock
or take a chance on a man of the slime