can these records be trusted
the Porkchives are the most comprehensive vault of knowledge in all the land
I assure you, High Councilman Ormid hails from the Slime Realm
surely a man born among The Slime™️ is not certainly a man of The Slime™️
who appointed Slimelord to the High Council of the Shard
Ormid
then we know where his allegiance lies
but think of all the good the Council has done under his guidance
it's been twelve years
surely if he was a man of The Slime™️
we would have seen through his guise
or perhaps he's biting his time until his plan unfurls
as we speak the Slimeguard is poised to strike
if Slimelord's been to the Shadow Realm
as you said he may now possess two of the Nether-Gems
what about the Blade
has the Porkwatch increased security
it's far from the city by now
Captain Greythorn is aboard the Porkaft in the Western Sea
and is taking the Blade to an unmarked island alone
I sent twp porkmen with him
Norgis and Fillik
they're good lads
good
Plaraxat help us all if the Slimeguard gets their hands on the Vlade
the Porkraft seems to be faring well tonight
Omnes Ad Porcos, Bother Norgis
she is a fine vessel
even in her old age
that she is Captain
I trust Fillik as fallen fast asleep
yes Captain
the waves have rocked him to sleep like a baby
ah well
he's earned it
and you should tuck in too Norgis
we sail at first light
once the Blade has been locked away
alright captain
the ocean's black is ink tonight isn't it
no one will find us out here
that's the plan brother
that's the plan