I didn't catch your name
John
nice to meet you John
and you are
also John
well
it's a pretty common name
you're telling me
I usually go by John J for that exact reason
you gotta be kidding me
don't tell me you're
John J
yeah
you're kidding
on my life man
John Jacob
really
don't tell me
yep
well we got about 8 billion people in the world
it's bound to be a couple John Jacobs
sure
I promise we don't have the same last name
wouldn't that be something
yeah man
I've never met another John Jacob Jingleheimer
Schmidt
yeah
how did
how did you know that
you know there can only be one
what
there can only be one
you don't have to do this
it's already done