last night at three bells past the twilight hour
a lone guardsman of the Porkwatch intercepted three men
attempting to steal the Crown of Elgnar
have the perpetrators been identified
markings on their robes indicate an affiliation with the Slimeguard
this can be seen as nothing but an act of aggression from the Slime Lord himself
we don't know that Tyrrill
and we will not jump to conclusions
they are members of the Slimeguard
they act at the behest of Slimelord
it is possible they act of their own accord
how can you be so quick to defend him
he has no place on this council
Braythwaite is right
it is possible they were not sent by Slimelord
surely you can't be serious
we sent him to negotiate with Gorlock
we've heard nothing and now he's come for the Crown
we will wait for the Porkwatch to conduct their investigation
before we jump to any conclusions
I agree with Ormid
for all we know Slime Lord is with Gorlock right now
negotiating for the release of the Shadow Stone
mark my words
while you wait for the Porkwatch
Slimelord will execute a second attack
I choose to believe he is a man of his word
he's a man of The Slime™
nothing more
I am in alignment with Braythwait
we will give him a chance to prove his allegiance
how can you do this
how can you continue to believe in him
because I am human
and I believe every man has a right
to his humanity
with all due respect, counselman
in my experience
Slimelord is no man