The High Council of the Shard was tasked with keeping peace within the realm
and yet there is turmoil
not just in our kingdom
but within the council itself
if you are troubled, Brother Ormid
allow your fellow councilmen to bear your load
I was approached by Thorranbarth of the Porkwatch
regarding the dealings of the Slimeguard
he suspects there are misdeeds within the council
and now I fear there is mistrust between us and the Watch
as long as the Lord of Slime sits on this council
our morals will be compromised
I fear that Brother Tyrrill is correct
we've not heard a word from Slimelord
since we sent him to the Shadow Realm to negotiate with Gorlock
we have no reason to believe that the Slimeguard did not act of their own accord
and given that the crown of Elgnar still sits safely within Borgan's Tower
I believe we must give Slimelord a chance to prove his allegiance
I now fear that my efforts to keep peace within the council
have caused greater chaos within the realm
the council must not rest until Slimelord is located
fortune smiles upon us that he did not procure the Crown of Elgnar
but how long will it be before the Slimeguard strikes again
in search of other ancient relics
I fear you are right brother
if Slimelord has truly returned to his dark ways
it won't be long before the realm is lost
I sense great sorrow within you
Brother Braythwaite
this is not the way of the Shard
it never was
the Shard demands understanding
but it also demands peace
and we shall see no peace
until Slimelord answers for the actions of the Slimeguard
then our path is clear dear brothers
we must go to the shadow realm
it should be me
I'm the one who started all of this
when I chose to trust the Slimelord