Councilman
Thorranbarth
Omnes Ad Porcos
Omnes Ad Porcos, brother
what brings you to the Temple of the Shard
Porkwatch footmen from the Outer Rim
have reported a disturbance in the Deadlands
you don't seem surprised
tell me Councilman
has the High Council of the Shard been tampering with the Shadow Gate
it is much more dire than that I'm afraid
Brother Braythwaite has ventured to the Realm of Shadows
High Councilman Ormid approved of this
he planned on going himself
but Brother Braythwaite has a history with the Shadow Lord
we thought it best that he negotiate with Gorlock
where is Ormis now
he's gone to the Shrine
should the Shard call to him
he desires to be close
it's best we not disturb him
I'll speak candidly, Tyrrill
I don't find within myself much trust for the High Council of the Shard
given that the Lord of the Slime™️ still holds a seat at the table
yes
I've expressed these very concerns from the beginning
you're the youngest on the council
you once served the Pork proudly
and now you answer to the Shard
but tell me this
do you trust your fellow councilmen
with my life
then brace yourself
because I've made a startling discovery
what do you mean
I went into the Porkives to see what I could find on the Lord of the Slime
but my search unearthed records that I'd never seen before
the high councilman is not who you think he is
this can't be true
I'm afraid it is
Brother Ormid
was born
in the Slime Realm