I just spoke with Thorranbarth of the Porkwatch
and as I predicted the Slimguard has seized yet another ancient relic
the Blade?
the Heart of Asloendrath
by Plaraxar's claw
forgive me brothers
by the power of the Shard
we are meant to see all things
but I fear I have become blind
we've no time to wallow Brother Ormid
Brother Braythwaite
we must hasten our descent into the Shadow Realm
Brother Tyrrill is correct
we've no time to dwell on the mistakes of the past
presently
Slime Lord is negotiating with Gorlock for the release of the Shadow Stone
and if he's been successful
he now possesses two of the Nether-Gems
we must act immediately or the realm will surely be lost
bring me my sword
no
what do you mean no
a battle will do no good in this realm or the realm of shadows
the Lord of the Simeâ„¢ï¸ is preparing for battle
Brother Braythwaite
we must come armed with more than words
look at me lads
did I not withdraw the Heart of Asloendrath from the cave of the Great Dragon
Plaraxar
you did
was it not I that fought in the Battle of a Thousand Jeremys
it was
and was it not I under the rule of his Majesty King Elgnar
that the Dark Lord Gorlock was banished to the Shadow Realm in the first place
yes dear brother
I may wear silver hair today
but I assure you my spirit is as strong as dwarven steel
the deepest lines on my body are not from age
they are scars
forgive us dear brother
go forth brother
Braythwaite
with the power of the Shard on your side
it would appear the Slime War has begun