after the Porkwatch intercepted members of the Slimeguard
attempting to steal the Crown of Elgnar
I met with Brother Ormid
of the High Council of the Shard to express my concerns
Brother Ormid is a man of honour
I have no doubt he was cooperative and receptive to your concerns
that's the thing, Captain
as far as I'm aware Brother Ormid
has made no effort to remove Slimelord from the High Council of the Shard
do you believe Slimelord is not worthy of a seat on the Council
Thorranbarth
you know as well as me, Captain
that he draws his power from The Slime™️
and the Slime Gate to this day remains open
and in the light of the recent actions of the Slimeguard
I don't see how we can trust the High Council of the Shard
given that the Slimelord sits among them
the men of the Shard have done more for this realm than
all the men of the pork combined
and that includes you Thorranbarth
so I'd ask that you choose your words wisely
I don't trust the Lord of the Slime
and as long as he sits on the Council of the Shard
I don't trust the Council either
these are incendiary words Thorranbarth
that they are, Captain
but what choice do I have
when I'm watching my kingdom burn
do you mean to tell me the Slimeguard struck again
last night they descended upon the temple and seized
the Heart of Asloendrath
the Crown
the Heart
it won't be long before they come for the Blade
and then the Slimeguard will be completely unstoppable
very well
assemble the Porkmen and tell the Blade-Keeper to move it to my ship
we must get the Blade as far from the city as possible
lest the Slimeguard strike again tonight
thank you, Captain
I believe that by acting now
we can stop this before the kingdom is completely consumed by The Slime™️
then go now in the name of The Pork™️
for now at least
the pork is one step ahead of the slime
I'm counting on it